I got married when I was quite young.
My husband and I met
right after we graduated high school.
I was just starting a new job.
After we were married,
I quit working,
and I've been a housewife ever since.
We were sadly never blessed with children,
so it's just been the two of us here.
This is us in Paris.
He took me when we were newlyweds.
That's my fondest memory.
- Blood pressure?
- No change.
- Could you give us some space, please?
- Sorry, yeah.
I received my cancer diagnosis first, but
it was my husband
who passed away before me.
I was alone.
My friends all said,
"How nice. You can finally live your life.
You're free to do anything you want."
But if I'm being honest,
I didn't know what to do. I was lost.
It's an emergency.
There just aren't enough doctors.
And the documentary's
keeping the director busy.
So we ask for help from the dark side.
Whoa! Like Mr. Spot Remover?
Or Ms. Backlash?
Mr. Spot Remover's one thing,
Ms. Backlash is something else.
We can't have people
finding out she works here.
- It would ruin us.
- We don't have any other choice.
When did I become interested
in cosmetic surgery?
When I saw it on TV.
Uh, Dr. Tohyama's father had that program.
They used to play it on,
uh, Tuesday nights.
I don't recall the name though.
Beauty Revolution.
That's it, yes.
I loved it. I watched it all the time.
Now it's time to see how our guest
has been transformed.
Come on out!
It's completely changed my life.
Oh, she looks like a star!
Incredible. Another amazing
transformation this week.
Just look at her!
Impressive as ever, Dr. Tohyama.
I'd call this another success.
The Hand of God can fix it all.
"The Hand of God can fix it all."
I loved that show.
Watched it every week.
- Oh yeah.
- Mm.
I thought if I were to get
that kind of surgery,
I'd put myself
in Dr. Tohyama's capable hands.
And what…
What if your husband were still with us?
Would you still get the operation?
I don't know…
Probably not.
Because he'd be against it?
Mm, no, it's nothing like that.
No, not at all.
It's more that, before he passed away,
I had never thought
to do anything for myself.
So this surgery is, uh,
something you're doing for yourself?
Yes.
DOCTOR TANUMA
- I already said that it's Numata.
- I know.
We want you to work under an alias.
We don't have enough doctors,
and we want you taking on new clients.
- No.
- You don't have to worry.
You'll be supported by Ms. Todoroki
every step of the way.
Mr. Ohashi, I understand
that you've requested
to speak with one of our doctors.
What would you like to discuss today?
Yeah.
It's, uh…
It's my palm lines.
His palm lines?
Thing is, I was born
with some serious bad luck.
Work's bad, but my relationships
are even worse.
And my… Well, my mom thinks
it's all because of my palm lines.
Yeah. You can see.
Here, my fate line,
my sun line, and my wealth line,
are all quite faint,
which indicates weakness.
And my mother thinks that if those three
were connected to my Hao line,
my luck would improve!
So… yeah.
SCULPTING THE FUTURE
I see. Well, first, let me say,
the palm has
a high concentration of nerve endings.
A careless incision
could cause scar contracture,
which could then become a source of pain.
Wait. I'd feel pain?
Not to mention, sir,
if changing the lines on your palm
could change your fate,
don't you think
everyone would be getting it done?
Well, that's, um…
- Um, so you're saying the Hao line is--
- Sir!
We'll do it for you.
I've heard that, in China,
the procedure has become quite the hit.
We'd be very pleased to help. I can't wait
to see how your future will change.
Really? Thank you, miss.
Marry me?
Ms. Todoroki!
I don't understand
why you booked the procedure
despite my professional opinion.
Because there was no reason to refuse it.
It can be done.
- Hang on a second.
- Also…
You need to stop mocking
your patients' concerns.
Mocking?
People come here
with problems they want solved.
Problems they've worried about.
And we help.
We don't look down on our patients
at this clinic.
Hm.
She actually took on the palm surgery?
But when did we start offering
that kind of treatment here?
Don't worry.
The point of cosmetic surgery
is the customer's satisfaction.
Though I doubt
he'll walk out with better luck.
Ah, so Dr. Backlash
might have to take another loss?
- Ms. Kato wants surgery today?
- Yes. She was insistent.
- Let's prepare Room B then.
- Of course.
Mm. It's payback.
Ms. Todoroki and Kanabun
were good friends, weren't they?
- Mm.
- Mm-hmm.
What? False advertising?
Yeah. We'll need a full list of any ads
that use the phrase "The Hand of God"
so we can scrub them.
Hang on, wait.
There must be some mistake.
We've been using it for years. My…
My dad coined it for his TV appearances.
I know that. But in the eyes of the law,
you're not a deity. You're a human being.
If a judge considers the phrase
to violate medical advertising guidelines,
we're cooked.
Right, so who's stirring up trouble?
It would appear to be the MBC Group.
SOTARO ANDO
MBC Group? Ha!
Their free surgeries scam
is making them millions.
- And they talk about ethics.
- Listen. We need to handle it.
There are some things that can be done
and some that can't.
Are you struggling with something?
Your new self begins right here.
From dream to reality.
You can be reborn.
The Hand of God
will change you.
You wanna bet she's had surgery too?
Yeah, apparently not.
There's pictures of her
as a kid going around.
…deserves beauty.
Including you.
Oh!
What a gross commercial.
It nearly ruins a perfectly good meal.
This again? Your mother hates the idea.
Plastic surgery.
When I told her I wanted some,
she practically divorced me.
What would you wanna get done, Dad?
You'll never know.
Of course. You shouldn't be
getting surgeries if you're not working.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Hey, I'm home!
- Oh, hi, Fumi.
- Hey.
Oh, I'm starving…
What's with all the food?
What the heck's going on?
Ah, Takashi! I thought I told you
to cut back on all this stuff.
Hey now, hang on. This is Macky's treat.
- Macky?
- Do we need more chopsticks?
Uh, it's been a minute.
Please. My friends call me Macky.
Look, I spent ages working on the broth,
so dig in, please!
- Dig in.
- Whoa, chawanmushi!
- It's chawanmushi.
- Sake?
- Let's do it!
- Hey.
What?
What do you think you're doing here?
I, um… It's chawanmushi, and I thought--
Listen, Fumi. Hang on.
- Get out, go.
- Takeru is--
Who gave you
the right to walk in here? Huh?
- Hey!
- Sis!
You goddamn loan shark.
You're a parasite. Get the hell out!
Get out!
- Like this, man.
- Oh, sure, yeah.
Good evening. May I have your name?
Is Director Ando available?
Yes. Just a moment please.
Takeru. Hey.
What's going on?
I'm coming in.
Huh?
Takeru!
Unlock the door!
Are you listening? What's wrong?
- Why did you kick him out?
- What?
I invited him.
I owe him.
What's that mean?
You know what kind of man he is.
Whatever. Just go away.
You blew up at him.
You didn't even want to hear Macky out.
Of course Takeru was pissed.
You've already forgotten
how shitty he's been to us?
No. But Macky's had a tough life,
too, you know.
He borrowed money from a loan shark
and wasn't able to pay him back,
so now he's got no choice
but to work as a debt collector.
Dunno why that should matter to me.
Well, because maybe
Takeru's taken a shine to him.
Don't start with that, okay?
I'll take care of Takeru.
- But you gotta stay out of it.
- That's out of the question. No.
- I gave birth to him. I can handle him.
- You had a C-section.
C-sections still hurt,
Miss High and Mighty.
I thought you were a doctor.
How do you not know?
Wait. Hang on a second.
Are you drinking?
- Give me that!
- Stop, no.
Give me the drink.
I'm not allowed green juice now?
Stop sticking your nose in my business.
Bitch.
Bitch?
Ah.
It's delicious. I love it.
Bitch?
I'm just trying to figure this out,
because it doesn't make any sense.
Why would the biggest chain in Japan
go after a clinic
with only three branches here?
I don't get it.
There's no point, you know?
Listen, Rin.
The fact is that Dr. Arata
made his name as The Hand of God.
And I understand that makes it
an important phrase for Tohyama Clinic.
And so?
Rin,
I was Dr. Arata's top student.
I've watched him perform surgery.
You don't have to tell me he's a genius.
I've seen it.
But that's Dr. Arata.
Why would I believe
you are as good as him?
- I think you're pushing it.
- I'm his chosen successor.
I don't remember
that privilege going to you,
Ando.
Which is why he passed
the "Hand of God" title on to me.
All that says is that he wanted
to keep the name in the family.
And that's not his style.
Sounds like something
a third-rate dictator would do.
He'd never stoop so low.
MBC was started for just that reason.
We're not getting anywhere.
We're clearly at a crossroad.
Sorry for dropping in on you
like this. Excuse me.
Are the rumors true?
That Dr. Arata is returning to practice?
- What?
- Yeah.
I'm sure it's nothing, but I heard a rumor
he's looking for property in Tokyo.
Absolutely not.
Thought so.
Coming back would just mean
putting you in a tough position.
Give it back.
Give me back my silicone.
Give it back!
Please don't come. I'm serious.
Now hang on.
You understand I can't just not go.
Because I'm a board member.
So what? I'm not going to school
if you show up.
What? What do you mean?
Can we keep it down? It's my day off
and you guys have to argue first thing?
Whatever. Just don't come!
- At least he's still in school.
- What?
This is all because of you
and your big mouth. You know that?
What am I supposed to do now?
Wait. Like… What's this about?
- There he is!
- Yeah, that's him. Come on.
- Yo, seriously?
- Hell yeah. Let's go. Come on.
Hey!
- Yo!
- Sup, loser?
Oh, sorry. We didn't realize
you were there.
Vroom, vroom.
- Vroom, vroom!
- See you around!
Why didn't you say anything?
Doesn't matter. Leave me alone.
And now, using a microscope, let's observe
the flow of blood in the capillaries.
After you've had a chance to observe,
talk with your group about what you see.
- Okay, yes, Miss.
- Go ahead.
Look! Look!
Hey, look. Is that her?
- The doctor who got cancelled!
- No way!
Whoa, that's crazy.
- Let's settle down, please.
- For real?
Quiet down, class. That's enough now!
Focus on your group discussions.
Takeru.
Where'd he go?
- Bathroom.
- Oh yeah?
- Excuse me. Are you Takeru's sister?
- Yes.
The PTA board meeting
is going to be starting at about noon.
- The board meeting?
- Yeah. Today.
- Thank you so much.
- Excuse me.
You want to film the facelift?
Yes. If we can.
Mr. Hamaguchi, I just want to make sure
that you understand the situation.
It's a complex surgery where we lift skin
from the face under general anesthesia.
Given Mrs. Yuriko's condition, it--
No, we understand.
We want to document the procedure
precisely because of the complexity.
Doctor, I've just got a feeling
this documentary's gonna go viral.
I promise we won't be in the way.
And it's not like we need a big crew.
Do you think you could make it work?
Hello, everyone, hello!
Sorry I'm late. Hello.
Ms. Osawa, you got another
hyaluronic acid treatment, didn't you?
- You can tell?
- Oh yeah, but who's counting?!
- Where? At Dr. Dong-yeon's?
- Exactly.
This is pretty much
what we always talk about.
Moms talk about cosmetic surgery now?
I never have that much to say myself.
How's your mother?
Is she doing any better? Was it cirrhosis?
Yeah, but she's okay now.
And I made her quit drinking.
Please, wish her well for me.
- Thanks.
- My pleasure.
Are you Takeru's sister?
- Yeah.
- It must have been difficult.
All the backlash to deal with.
We were all shocked.
And very concerned.
Weren't we?
Oh. Well, I'm sorry if I was a burden.
Takeru will be fine.
The PTA will take charge
of communicating with the school.
He'll have what he needs.
It's all under control.
Right.
Mom?
Oh, Mikana. Hey, sweetie.
You came all the way out here
again to shop?
The trick is to come after 4 p.m.,
when things get marked down.
Come on, that's so embarrassing.
And you wore that outfit
to the last PTA meeting.
What? I didn't. Or did I?
Oh, wow. How could you forget that?
Okay, don't worry. I don't think
anyone cares about my clothes.
Oh, hey, have you talked to Dad yet
about me studying abroad?
Uh, maybe he should hear it from you.
But he always just says to ask you anyhow.
Please, Mom?
Yua and Sana's parents already said yes.
- I'm back.
- Oh, welcome home.
My manager invited me
out for drinks and I'm feeling it.
- I'll just have something light.
- Oh.
So Mikana and I were talking…
Yeah?
And she wants to study abroad in Hawaii
over summer break.
Her best friends are going, apparently.
Yeah, sure. Let her do it.
But the exchange rates
are rough right now.
The program's not going to be cheap.
Budgeting for the household is your job.
You'll think of something.
Sure. I guess.
I was wondering if I should get a job too.
Where'd you get that idea?
Well, with two incomes,
we would have more options.
Fewer women stay home.
Most of them go back to work eventually.
I don't wanna have
this conversation again.
You agreed to be a stay-at-home mom
until Mikana graduates.
Besides, you've been out of the workforce
for ten years. Who would hire you?
I won't have you
working at some supermarket.
It's embarrassing.
Don't even think about it.
I guess you're right.
Welcome back. What will happen?
Are you ready to play?
Mr. Watanabe's blood work
results were due to arrive today.
Do you know if they did?
The fate line.
- I'll ask. Be right back.
- Sounds good.
Dr. Tanuma's final battle
is about to begin.
You hold your patient's future
in your hands.
Ms. Yuriko, are you feeling comfortable?
Yes. I'm fine, thanks.
Before we begin,
I'd like to ask you
about something important.
Go on.
This, ma'am,
is the contract we signed before today.
It states that we won't film
any of the procedures
performed under general anesthesia.
However, the documentary director
asked if we could make an exception.
MEMORANDUM
If it's all right with you, Ms. Yuriko,
we'd like your permission
to film your surgery.
THIS IS TRIBEAU, THE COSMETIC BOOKING APP!
BROWSE CLINICS BY BODY PART
- Administering anesthesia--
- Doctor, wait.
Um Is there some way that we can
make the injection painless too?
- How long?
- 20 minutes.
- We've applied the anesthetic.
- Right.
All right, here we go.
Beginning the procedure.
Ah, it hurts.
You can feel this?
Uh, well, it hurts.
So, you can?
YURIKO SAKASHITA
Excellent. Thank you so much.
Great. Let's hope
the documentary is a hit.
Yes. The next step is the tests, then?
Doctor?
- Ms. Yuriko.
- Yes?
I'd like to recommend that
you reconsider your planned surgery.
What?
You've made some great progress
so far, Ms. Yuriko,
and you're already so beautiful.
I don't really understand
why you'd want to undergo a facelift.
Doctor, you were the one who said
it would give me the best results.
And that is true.
However,
it's also true
that it will put a lot of stress--
Yes, I'm well aware of the risks, Doctor.
But if this surgery can change me,
if it can make me beautiful,
then I want to take the risk.
I'm not like you.
This may be my only opportunity!
I understand.
COSMETIC SURGERY TURNED MY LIFE AROUND
Doctor, it's not like
the surgery's that dangerous, is it?
I mean, as your legal counsel,
I need to be very clear that if
the unthinkable were to happen
during the filming--
She signed the consent form, didn't she?
She's already made up her mind, okay?
All right then.
Guess I'll be going.
Dearest God…
…this man desires better luck.
Improve his fortune, God.
A doctor praying for help with a patient.
Is that a problem?
I just wonder about the optics of it.
It's more that
I don't think my skills
can improve a patient's luck.
But don't worry.
I'll stay on the dark side.
I can even study up on spot removal.
Actually,
why are you here?
You're not praying
for help with a patient?
- That's not a problem, I hope?
- Nah.
Ironic.
That The Hand of God
would be praying to God.
Have a good day.
I have a feeling we're going
to work up a sweat. It's so warm today.
- Oh! I'm sorry, dear.
- Is everything all right?
Why don't we sit down?
Here, take your time. Rest.
There.
I'm going to take
Ms. Yuriko home now, Doctor.
Would you mind coming with me?
Go with you?
Having a doctor would be better.
Both the director and Dr. Rui
have appointments, you see.
Just give me a minute.
- Let's take it easy.
- Of course. Thank you, dear.
- I'll take your blood pressure.
- Sorry for the trouble.
I barely went out and I'm already dizzy.
Can you believe it?
- Ms. Yuriko?
- Yes?
Does the filming bother you?
No, not at all. It's funny,
it makes me feel like I'm dreaming.
My husband would be so shocked
if he could see me now.
Blood pressure's a little low.
Right.
- Ms. Yuriko?
- Yes?
I'd like you to rest for a few days.
Yes.
Is everything all right?
- Labored breathing.
- I'll go get a towel.
Ms. Yuriko,
I'd like to listen to your lungs.
It'll be over soon. I'm completely fine.
- Ms. Yuriko.
- Hm?
It would seem that the cancer
may have spread to your lungs.
I'd like to call an ambulance.
No, no, it'll stop soon.
I have to, for your own good
Don't do it!
Please don't. I hate hospitals.
Here. You can rinse your mouth.
No. I'm sorry. I can't do this anymore.
I don't think you understand.
Your life is in danger, facelift or no.
If you keep pushing with no regard
for the consequences, it's pointless.
You don't understand, Doctor.
It doesn't matter if I die.
I just want them to leave me alone!
They told me the same thing
at the hospital.
But doctors don't…
They don't care about
how their patients feel. Not really.
They just pity us and look down on us.
- They don't. That's not true.
- They do!
They all do, and so do you.
You think I'm stupid, don't you, Doctor?
Despite what my body's going through,
I still want to be beautiful.
And you pity me!
You think I'm pathetic, don't you?
You should rest. Lie back.
I'm nearing the end.
I know. I know I am.
And at the end, I just…
I wanted to do something
that was just for me and no one else.
That's all I really want now.
Even if the thing I want is silly or vain.
Over the course of my life, I've learned
everyone has needs.
All of us.
Important or frivolous.
We all need something
that means the world to us.
I never deliberately looked down on her.
I never pitied her. I swear.
Is that how it was with Kana?
- Sorry?
- Kanabun.
You thought it was ridiculous
to get implants when she had a tumor.
That's not looking down on her?
I happen to agree with Ms. Yuriko,
as hard as it may be to accept.
As much as you may not want
to admit it, Doctor.
I'm home.
Hi, honey. Do you mind having dinner now?
Uh, because Daddy's late.
He's still working?
He just texted, yeah.
I bet it's another drinking party.
Oh, right, so about you studying overseas,
well, Poppa said yeah!
He did? For real?
On one condition. You have to come back
even smarter than you are now. Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Now let's eat!
I'll kill myself!
Let me be clear.
I had to take the silicone out
because you were in critical condition
and about to die.
If I hadn't taken it out, you might
have died! What don't you get, you moron?
I wanna die!
Despite what my body's going through,
I still want to be beautiful.
And you pity me!
You think I'm pathetic, don't you?
Unknown number.
- Hello?
- Hi.
It's Numata.
Yes?
I need to ask you for a favor.
Hi! How are you? Just these.
- You've got a lot today.
- Yeah, we've got a lot of stuff today.
Let me take a look.
UPDATE ON DRY CLEANING PRICES
Uh, sorry. It'll just be the suit, please.
I forgot something at home.
I, um…
I need to tell you--
You're the doctor from the university.
I've seen your picture online.
Yes.
I didn't know Ms. Kana well…
but for her, there was something
more valuable than life.
I couldn't understand that.
There's nothing I can do
that will bring her back.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry, ma'am.
I would have done the same thing
if I were you.
What?
She had a tumor,
but still wanted her implants.
It's crazy. It's unreasonable.
Any doctor would think that.
But here's the thing.
That was the only way
she knew how to live.
Up until junior high, she was a shut-in.
But when she started getting surgery,
her life was transformed.
She got scouted by a modeling agency.
People knew her. They loved her.
She shined so bright
that she became a star.
Deep down, though,
she was in terrible agony.
She was suffering
because none of it was real.
None of it. It was all a lie.
Her date of birth, her hometown,
her graduation photo,
her Wikipedia page.
Even the name, Kana Kokubun.
It was all made-up.
It was crafted, just like her appearance.
She…
She was so desperate to hide her pain.
But she could never outrun it.
I always knew
it would end up catching her one day.
This was my daughter.
She was more real than Kanabun.
Her name was Akari Shimoda.
I looked into the rumors about the
chairman renting a property for a clinic.
From what I could tell,
it seems to be true.
He's aiming to have it in operation
by the end of the year.
And so,
would you like me to try to find out more
about the chairman's plans for the clinic?
Ma'am?
There's no need.
I'll just ask him myself
the next time I see him. Thank you.
SUCCESSOR OF THE HAND OF GOD
- Good morning.
- Today's the day.
- Yes.
Time for the facelift.
- Beautiful day for it.
- Yes, it's gorgeous, isn't it?
There's talk that the Tohyama
director made a critical medical error,
and that a lot of clients
are leaving for other clinics.
What is it, Rin?
The fact is that Dr. Arata
made his name as "The Hand of God."
But that's Dr. Arata.
Why would I believe you're as good as him?
I think you're pushing it.
Ah, this is great. Wow.
Is this doctor supposed to be me?
So then, this one must be you, Rin.
I see.
Well, then, you must want to be a doctor,
just like Daddy.
You must want to be a doctor,
Now we can't film?
Come on, Doctor.
I was just with her. She was excited.
The decision has nothing
to do with Mrs. Yuriko.
It was a clinic-wide amendment.
I understand, Doctor,
but it's just so sudden.
Raise the right side by 0.5 millimeters.
Dr. Rui.
Would you mind giving us a minute, please?
Mm. Sure.
Yes? What is it?
I wanted to speak to you
about Mrs. Yuriko's facelift.
I want you to perform her surgery.
What?
Impossible.
I don't get it. Why?
We don't have time
to get into the details. I'm sorry.
But rest assured,
I'll be there to support you.
No! I refuse to do it.
And you knew I would refuse.
I was against her getting the surgery
to begin with. You know that!
I can't be the only option to perform it.
Unless you decided it was too dangerous.
It'd explain why you're making me do it.
- It's not like that.
- Then why me?
It can't be me. It has to be you!
If anything does go wrong,
I'll assume all responsibility.
My dress shirts have to be
dry cleaned. I told you, didn't I?
It's just that the
dry cleaner's is so expensive. I thought--
You thought what? You can't be serious.
What could it cost? A hundred yen? Two?
I guess. I… I know it doesn't seem
like much, but it can really add up.
You know
what your problem is? You're cheap.
I'm not asking for much. Am I?
All I'm asking for is for you
to do something simple. Isn't that right?
Mm-hmm. I'm sorry, you're right.
- I know.
- No problem.
I'll take them now, then.
I'm such a scatterbrain.
Last-minute cancellations suck.
Oh yeah.
- Oh! Here she comes.
- Hey, roll camera!
Rolling.
Here comes The Hand of God. Get a shot.
All right, Ms. Yuriko.
If you're ready, we'll begin.
I'm ready. I'm in your hands, Doctor.
As soon as she's out of surgery,
we'll be ready, okay?
Yes, of course.
This way.
Just in here.
Administering anesthetic.
Good.
Doctor, we're ready for you now.
Beginning with the skin incision.
- Scalpel.
- Swap out the gauze.
- Okay.
Director, look at her blood pressure.
It's all right.
You can continue.
I'm not gonna study abroad.
Wait, what? Where's this coming from?
I've been saving up for you to go.
Your father and I
have both made sacrifices for this.
You mean you've made sacrifices.
Come on. That's not fair,
and it's not even true.
Mom, you're not happy, are you?
You never get new clothes for yourself.
You buy groceries really far away.
I do that because I want to.
I like the exercise--
No. I don't believe you!
Honey…
That store's the best.
They have great cuts of meat,
the produce is always fresh--
- No, stop lying to me!
- I'm not lying to you!
Mommy's happy living here
with you and your father.
I'm not giving anything up.
I don't think she can handle any more.
- Director, this is--
- I'll help with the sutures.
- Let's hurry.
- Ms. Takahashi, raise the bed.
- Turning her head.
- Careful.
There we go.
Wipe the incision, please.
Thank you.
Mom, you're not happy, are you?
Sorry!
- It's okay.
- Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine. I'm fine. Sorry. Thanks.
Sorry.
Is it finished? How is Ms. Yuriko?
She's doing well.
The surgery was a success.
Five hours.
That was long.
I had no idea that the surgery
would be this complicated.
I'm sorry.
You can film now.
- Right, let's go.
- Okay.
Excuse us.
Excuse us. We'll stay out of your way.
- Excuse us.
- Shoot from that side.
You got it.
- Wow.
- Hi. Sorry.
Kana's mom called.
She said that you two had a talk
and that you apologized.
Thank you for that.
Oh. No, I'm the one that should thank you.
Really. Thanks.
Who's staying here tonight? You?
I'm not, no. It's the director.
The director?
She's been sleeping here ever
since Ms. Yuriko's surgery was booked.
Wanted to stay close.
She worries, even if she doesn't show it.
If she says she wants to die, you'll just
kill her? You lost your damn mind?
Someone who doesn't have much time left
is asking for one last chance
to be beautiful!
I'm a doctor. How can I deny her that?
Life isn't just quantity.
It's also quality.
There are ways to help
besides chemotherapy.
Huh. She's known for a while.
The counseling session.
That's when she realized it.
What?
That Ms. Yuriko
wouldn't be satisfied
with only a longer life.
Honestly, I, um…
I never thought about it like that before.
I looked into the rumors
about the chairman
renting a property for a clinic.
It seems to be true.
Mikana, can I come in? I wanna talk.
I'm not hungry.
No, it's not that, honey.
It's about studying overseas.
Go on, take it. If it makes you happy,
then you should do it.
You know what? I've decided
I want to do what makes me happy too.
I have some money
I've been saving up in secret.
A walk-in?
That's right. She wanted
to have the work done today.
And I thought I'd at least ask
since one of your operations
was cancelled this afternoon.
- Pencil her in.
- Of course, Doctor.
What surgery is it she's asking about?
Don't be nervous.
The doctors here are wonderful. Very kind.
- Come in.
- Ma'am?
Go on in.
You can put your personal items
on the couch.
Excuse me. The woman
who just came in, what's she here for?
Oh, female genital surgery.
What procedure?
A labia minora reduction.
It's funny, though.
Doing that before her face
is like jumping straight to third base.
Maybe her husband lost interest
after she gave birth.
Yikes! That does happen.
- It's hard, though.
- It is, for sure.
Some patients choose to change
their appearance for themselves.
And she is one of them.
Her husband has nothing to do with it.
She told me she wanted to feel
more confident in her body.
Whether or not they can be seen,
insecurities plague all of us.
It's our job to support people.
- I'm sorry, Doctor.
- Sorry, Doctor.
- Let me know if it hurts, okay?
- I will. Thank you.
All right, we're starting. This may sting.
Okay.
That's done.
Now we'll start the procedure.
If you feel any discomfort, we can
up the anesthetic. Just let us know.
Yes.
Hi, Mrs. Ozawa. We're all done.
What?
You're…
It's over?
Yes, it's all over now.
Is that all right?
I bet you thought
it was going to be a much bigger surgery.
No, it's just that…
I was just wondering why it took so long
for me to do something so simple.
And the more I think about it,
the more I feel silly.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
I'm sorry.
You did so great.
Even if the thing I want is silly or vain.
Over the course of my life, I've learned
everyone has needs.
All of us.
We all need something
that means the world to us.
Doctor, here's your mark. Stand here.
Thank you. Perfect. We're ready?
- Ready, sir.
- Let's roll it.
- Okay, sound speed.
- Speeding.
- Camera.
- Rolling.
We're rolling.
And we're on!
Bring her in three, two…
Cue.
Ms. Yuriko, congratulations.
Please, take these.
Thank you so much.
You look so incredibly beautiful.
Here, this way.
What do you think?
I think I can now die happy.
Oh, enough of that, Ms. Yuriko.
Enjoy your beauty and your new life.
I hate to say it, but a GP would never
be able to do what she did, would they?
- What are you…
- The chairman?
What are you doing here?
I got a call from a pushy TV director.
He asked me if I would check
the final result of the surgery.
My name is Tohyama.
Do you mind if I have a look at you?
Please.
I'm surprised.
She's perfect.
Oh, jeez…
You had me on edge there for a minute.
Congratulations, ma'am.
You're absolutely stunning.
Thank you so much.
Hi, ma'am, welcome.
- Those look great.
- Would you like some? Here you go, then.
- Thanks. Bye.
- Thank you.
Hello. How--
Uh, Mikana…
Mom, what…
Caught red-handed!
Mm. I was
just putting out some fresh fruit.
PHOTO STUDIO MATSUO
Oh! Hello there.
Hello.
Do I…
Ah!
I'm sorry, I didn't recognize you.
You look so different.
I believe the last time you came
was for your husband.
Yes. It was for his memorial.
- Ah, yes, that's right.
- Yeah.
Are you here to celebrate something, then?
I was going to ask you
to take my memorial photo.
Sorry, I don't understand.
Your memorial photo?
Yes.
So, what did you end up getting?
- Hm?
- You used your secret savings.
Can't tell you.
Why not? That's not fair! I wanna know.
I can't tell you now.
But I can tell you
when you graduate from college.
College? Mom, that's, like, so far away.
You'd be surprised how fast it'll go.
Well, your dad will be home late tonight.
Wanna go get something to eat?
Really? Amazing! Yay! Where are we going?
I think you might already know.
Ah… Back to Saize?
I love Saize's, don't you?
Yeah, I do too.
Okay, is there something you'd
rather eat? Tell me. We'll go anywhere.
Hm… What do I want?
Are you ready?
I can't lie, Rin. I'm impressed.
Who would have dared
to do such an intensive procedure
on a terminal cancer patient?
If it airs,
it may well bring a lot of new clients.
When I first heard those rumors,
I was worried, I can't lie.
But you've put my mind at ease.
And speaking of rumors,
there's something I've been meaning
to ask you about as well, actually.
Before that, let me say…
I wouldn't be much of a father
if all I ever did was praise you
without offering feedback.
To be honest with you, her nose…
I wasn't that impressed.
You can do better.
The final shape was ordinary at best.
Hm. Certainly not worthy of our clinic.
Oh. Now, don't make that face.
It wasn't all bad. Right?
The facelift was perfect.
I mean it.
It was truly
the work of my successor, Rin.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Thanks, Dad.
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
DOCTOR TANUMA
Tanuma? Her name's Numata. Idiots.
TOHYAMA COSMETIC SURGERY CLINIC
Hey, Macky! What's up?
What are you doing here?
Just walking by, you know.
Just figured I'd say hi.
See how you were doing.
I mean it.
It was truly
the work of my successor, Rin.